(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Nice to meet you, where you been?
I could show you incredible things Magic, madness,
heaven, sin Saw you there and I thought,
oh my god Look at that face, you
look like My next mistake Love's a game,
wanna play New money, suit and tie I
can read you like a magazine Ain't it
funny, rumors fly And I know you heard
about me, so hey Let's be friends, I'm
dying to see How this one ends Grab
your passport in my hand I can make
the bad guys good for a weekend So
it's gonna be forever Or it's gonna go
down in flames You can tell me when
it's over If the high was worth the
pain Got a long list of ex-lovers
They'll tell you I'm insane Cause you know
I love the players And you love the
game Cause we don't give a reckless We'll
take this way too far It'll leave you
breathless Or with a nasty scar Got a
long list of ex-lovers They'll tell you
I'm insane But I've got a blank space,
baby And I'll write your name Cherry lips,
crystal skies I could show you incredible things
Stolen kisses, pretty lies You're the king, baby,
I'm your queen Find out what you want
Be that girl for a month Wait, the
worst is yet to come Oh no Screaming,
crying, perfect storms I can make all the
tables turn Loves gotten good with thorns Keep
you sick and get you like Oh my
god, who is she?
I get drunk on jealousy But you'll come
back each time you leave Cause darling, I'm
a nightmare Dressed like a daydream So it's
gonna be forever Or it's gonna go down
in flames You can tell me when it's
over If the high was worth the pain
Got a long list of ex-lovers They'll
tell you I'm insane Cause you know I
love the players And you love the game
You're young, you're reckless You'll take this way
too far It'll leave you breathless Or hit
the nasty scar Got a long list of
ex-lovers They'll tell you I'm insane But
I've got a blank space, baby And I'll
write your name Boys only want love If
it's torture Don't say I didn't Say I
didn't warn ya Boys only want love If
didn't warn ya So it's gonna be forever
Or it's gonna go down in flames You
can tell me when it's over If the
high was worth the pain Got a long
list of ex-lovers They'll tell you I'm
insane Cause you know I love the players
And you love the game You're young, you're
reckless You'll take this way too far It'll
leave you breathless Or hit the nasty scar
Got a long list of ex-lovers They'll
tell you I'm insane But I've got a
blank space, baby And I'll write your name