(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Hey, I was doing just fine before I
met you I drink too much and that's
an issue, but I'm okay Hey, you tell
your friends it was nice to meet them
But I hope I never see them again
I know it breaks your heart, moved to
the city and I broke down crying Four
years, no call, now you're looking pretty in
a hotel bar and I can't stop, no
I can't stop So baby pull me closer
in the backseat of your Rover That I
know you can't afford, bite that tattoo on
your shoulder Pull the sheets right off the
corner of the mattress that you stole From
your roommate back in Boulder, we ain't ever
getting older We ain't
ever getting older You
look as good as the day I met
you I forget just why I left you,
I was insane Stay, and play that Pink
Winter Uni 2 song Velvet beat to death
in Tucson, okay I know it breaks your
heart, moved to the city and I broke
down crying Four years, no call, now you're
looking pretty in a hotel bar and I
can't stop, no I can't stop So
baby pull me closer in the backseat of
your Rover That I know you can't afford,
bite that tattoo on your shoulder Pull the
sheets right off the corner of the mattress
that you stole From your roommate back in
Boulder, we ain't ever getting older We
ain't ever getting older We
ain't ever getting older So baby pull me
closer in the backseat of your Rover That
I know you can't afford, bite that tattoo
on your shoulder Pull the sheets right off
the corner of the mattress that you stole
From your roommate back in Boulder, we ain't
ever getting older