(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) This night is cold in the kingdom.
I can feel you fade away.
From the kitchen to the bathroom, sinking.
Your steps keep me awake.
Don't cut me down, throw me out, leave
me here to waste.
I once was a man with dignity and
grace.
Now I'm slipping through the cracks of your
cold embrace.
So please, please, could you find a way
to let me down slowly?
A little sympathy, I hope you can show
me.
If you wanna go, then I'll be so
lonely.
If you're leaving, baby, let me down slowly.
Let me down, down, let me down, down,
let me down, let me down, down, let
me down, down, let me down.
If you wanna go, then I'll be so
lonely.
If you're leaving, baby, let me down slowly.
Cold skin drag my feet on the tile,
as I'm walking down the corridor.
And I know we haven't talked in a
while, so I'm looking for an open door.
Don't cut me down, throw me out, leave
me here to waste.
I once was a man with dignity and
grace.
Now I'm slipping through the cracks of your
cold embrace.
So please, please, could you find a way
to let me down slowly?
A little sympathy, I hope you can show
me.
If you wanna go, then I'll be so
lonely.
If you're leaving, baby, let me down slowly.
Let me down, down, let me down, down,
let me down, let me down, down, let
me down, down, let me down.
If you wanna go, then I'll be so
lonely.
If you're leaving, baby, let me down slowly.
And I can't stop myself from falling Down
Could you find a way to let me
down slowly?
A little sympathy, I hope you can show
me If you wanna go, then I'll be
so lonely If you're leaving, baby, let me
down slowly Let me down, down, let me
down, down, let me down Let me down,
down, let me down, down, let me down
If you wanna go, then I'll be so
lonely If you're leaving, baby, let me down
slowly If you wanna go, then I'll be
so lonely If you're leaving, baby, let me
down slowly