(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Going out tonight, changes into something red Her
mother doesn't like that kind of dress Everything
she never had, she's showing off Driving too
fast, moon is breaking through her hair She's
heading for something that she won't forget Having
no regrets is all that she really wants
We're only getting older baby And I've been
thinking about it lately Does it ever drive
you crazy Just how fast the night changes
Everything that you've ever dreamed of Disappearing when
you wake up But there's nothing to be
afraid of Even when the night changes It
will never change me and you Chasing it
tonight, doubts are running round her head He's
waiting, hides behind a cigarette Heart is beating
loud and she doesn't want it to stop
Moving too fast, moon is lighting up her
skin She's falling, doesn't even know it yet
Having no regrets is all that she really
wants We're only getting older baby And I've
been thinking about it lately Does it ever
drive you crazy Just how fast the night
changes Everything that you've ever dreamed of Disappearing
when you wake up But there's nothing to
be afraid of Even when the night changes
It will never change me and you Going
out tonight, changes into something red Her mother
doesn't like that kind of dress Reminds her
of a missing piece of innocence she lost
We're only getting older baby And I've been
thinking about it lately Does it ever drive
you crazy Just how fast the night changes
Everything that you've ever dreamed of Disappearing when
you wake up But there's nothing to be
afraid of Even when the night changes Everything
that you've ever dreamed of Disappearing when you
wake up But there's nothing to be afraid
of Even when the night changes It will
never change baby It will never change
me and you