(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) I love it when you call me señorita,
I wish I could pretend I didn't need
ya.
But every touch is ooh la la la,
it's true la la la.
Ooh, I should be runnin', ooh, you keep
me comin' for ya.
That in Miami, the air was hot from
summer rain sweat drippin' off me.
Before I even knew her name, la la
la.
You felt like ooh la la la, yeah,
no.
Sapphire moonlight, we danced for hours in the
scent of tequila sunrise.
Her body felt right in my hands like
la la.
You felt like ooh la la la, yeah.
I love it when you call me señorita,
I wish I could pretend I didn't need
ya.
But every touch is ooh la la la,
it's true la la la.
Ooh, I should be runnin', ooh, you know.
I love it when you call me señorita,
I wish it wasn't so damn hard to
leave ya.
But every touch is ooh la la la,
it's true la la la.
Ooh, I should be runnin', ooh, you keep
me comin' for ya.
Back in the hotel, there's just some things
that never change.
You say we're just friends, but friends don't
know the way it tastes.
La la la.
Girl, you know it's been a long time
comin', don't you let me fall.
Open your lips and just be hooked on
your tongue.
All of your kisses, they don't stop.
I love it when you call me señorita,
I wish I could pretend I didn't need
ya.
But every touch is ooh la la la,
it's true la la la.
Ooh, I should be runnin', ooh, you know.
I love it when you call me señorita,
I wish it wasn't so damn hard to
leave ya.
But every touch is ooh la la la,
it's true la la la.
Ooh, I should be runnin', ooh, you keep
me comin' for ya.
All along I've been comin' for ya.
All along I've been hopin' that something's real.
You call my name, I'll be comin' for
ya.
Comin' for ya.
For ya.
Ooh, I should be runnin', ooh, you keep
me comin' for ya.
For ya.