(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) The club isn't the best place to find
a lover, so the bar is where I
go.
Me and my friends sat at the table
doing shots, drinking fast and then we talked
slow.
And you come over and start up a
conversation with just me, and trust me I'll
give it a chance.
Now take my hand, stop, and the man
on the jukebox, and then we start to
dance.
And I'm singing like, girl you know I
want your love, your love was handmade for
somebody like me.
Come on now, follow my lead, I may
be crazy, don't mind me.
Say boy, let's not talk too much, grab
on my waist and put that body on
me.
Come on now, follow my lead, come, come
on now, follow my lead.
I'm in love with the shape of you,
we push and pull like a magnet do.
Although my heart is falling too, I'm in
love with your body.
Last night you were in my room, and
now my bed sheets smell like you.
Everyday discovering something brand new, I'm in love
with your body.
with the shape of you.
And we came and we let the story
begin, we're going out on our first date.
You and me, you're thrifty so go all
you can eat, fill up your bag and
I fill up the plate.
We talk for hours and hours about the
sweet and the sour, and how your family's
doing okay.
And we've been getting a taxi, kissing the
back seat, tell the driver make the radio
play.
And I'm singing like, girl you know I
want your love, your love was handmade for
somebody like me.
Come on now, follow my lead, I may
be crazy, don't mind me.
Say boy, let's not talk too much, grab
on my waist and put that body on
me.
Come on now, follow my lead, come, come
on now, follow my lead.
I'm in love with the shape of you,
we push and pull like a magnet do.
Although my heart is falling too, I'm in
love with your body.
Last night you were in my room, now
I bet she'd smell like you.
Everyday discovering something brand new, I'm in love
with your body.
I'm in love with your body.
Oh I, oh I, oh I, oh I.
Everyday discovering something brand new, I'm in love
with the shape of you.
Come on, be my
baby,
come on.
I'm in love with the shape of you,
we push and pull like a magnet do.
Although my heart is falling too, I'm in
love with your body.
Last night you were in my room, now
I bet she'd smell like you.
Everyday discovering something brand new, I'm in love
with your body.
I'm in love with your body.
Come on, be my baby, come on.
Everyday discovering something brand new, I'm in love
with the shape of you.