(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) He said,
let's get out of this town Drive out
of the city, away from the crowds I
thought heaven can't help me now Nothing lasts
forever But this is gonna take me down
He's so tall and handsome as hell He's
so bad, but he does it so well
I can see the end as it begins
My one condition is Say you'll remember me
Standing in a nice dress Staring at the
sunset, babe Red lips and nosy cheeks Say
you'll see me again Even if it's just
in your wildest dreams I
said, no one has to know what we
do His hands are in my hair, his
clothes are in my room And his voice
is a familiar sound Nothing lasts forever But
this is getting good now He's so tall
and handsome as hell He's so bad, but
he does it so well And when we've
had our very last kiss My last request
is Say you'll remember me Standing in a
nice dress Staring at the sunset, babe Red
lips and nosy cheeks Say you'll see me
again Even if it's just in your wildest
dreams Wildest dreams You'll
see me in hindsight Hang about with you
all night, but it's a doubt Someday when
you leave me I bet these memories will
do you well You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night, but it's
a doubt Someday when you leave me I
bet these memories will do you well You'll
see me in hindsight Hang about with you
all night, but it's a doubt Say you'll
remember me Standing in a nice dress Staring
at the sunset, babe Red lips and nosy
cheeks Say you'll see me again Even if
it's just pretend Say you'll remember me Standing
in a nice dress Staring at the sunset,
babe Red lips and nosy cheeks Say you'll
see me again Even if it's just in
your wildest dreams Wildest
dreams Even if it's just in your wildest
dreams